{
  "levels": [
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Pusa \n\nBicolano:___",
      "correctAnswer": "Ikos",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Ikoy",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Langgam"
    },
    {
      "question": "Batangueno: Guyam \n\nTagalong:___",
      "correctAnswer": "Langgam",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Chewing gum",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Hipon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Buhok \n\nPangasinense:_____",
      "correctAnswer": "Buwek",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Luwek",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Bahuk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ampetang:Pangasinense \n\nTagalog:____",
      "correctAnswer": "Mainit",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Malamig",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Maligamgam"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Sitaw \n\nIlocano:____",
      "correctAnswer": "Utong",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Baktong",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Kutang"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Maganda \n\nWaray:___",
      "correctAnswer": "Maanyag",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Kaanyag",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Kaanyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ilocano:Napekpek \n\nTagalog:_____",
      "correctAnswer": "Napuno",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Gabi",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Hapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Maliit \n\nBassit:____",
      "correctAnswer": "Ilocano",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Hiligaynon",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Batangueño"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ag-Tagainep:Ilocano \n\nTagalog:_____",
      "correctAnswer": "Panaginip",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Sumilip",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Ahit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tagalog:Mahal \n\nPangga:____",
      "correctAnswer": "Kapampangan",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Bisaya",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Pangasinense"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gabok:Batangueño \n\nTagalog:_____",
      "correctAnswer": "Alikabok",
      "wrongAnswer1": "Alingasaw",
      "wrongAnswer2": "Agiw"
    }
  ]
}

